The Game View in Unity is invoked when the Play button is pressed.
Unity のゲームビューは Play ボタンが押されたとき実行されます。
In this you can play test your game and get an idea
この中でゲームのテスト実行を行って
of what the gameplay will be like when it's built.
ビルドしたときのゲームプレイがどうなるか確認できます。
This can be paused and stepped forward at any time
いつでもポーズして、ステップ実行が出来て、
in order to give you more accurate testing.
より正確なテストが可能となります。
You can also tweak things whilst you are in play mode
再生モードあるときに色々なものを調整することが出来て、
in order to see what the game play is like with different settings.
異なる設定でゲームプレイがどうなるか確認できます。
The game view also allows you to set resolution
ゲームビューにより使用しているターゲットプラットフォームにあわせた
specific to the target platform that you're using.
解像度をセットすることが出来ます。
For example my game view is set to Standalone
例えばゲームビューはスタンドアローンにセットされていて
with a resolution of 1280 by 720.
解像度は 1280 x 720 です。
If I choose to then maximise on play
もし再生するときに最大化（Maximize On Play）を選択すると
the game view will restrict to exactly that resolution
ゲームビューはちょうどその解像度となります。
so that I can see what it will look like.
これにより、表示がどうなるか確認できます。
To adjust this I go to Edit - Project Settings - Player
調整するためには Edit - Project Settings - Player と選択すれば
and this shows me the default
Resolution の下にデフォルトの
screen width and height under resolution.
スクリーン幅と高さが表示されます。
If I edit this
編集をすると
I will see the change made immediately in the game view.
行った変更はただちにゲームビューに反映されて表示されます。
And if I choose to switch to a different target platform
さらに別のターゲットプラットフォームに切り替えて選択すると
I will get the resolution for that setting.
その設定の解像度に変化します。
For example if I switch to Web Player
例えばウェブプレイヤーに切り替えて
and return
戻ると、
Web Player is then featured
ウェブプレイヤーが
as the target platform I'm building for
ビルド対象のターゲットプラットフォームとなり
and the preview mode for the game view.
ゲームビューのプレビューモードとなります。
In addition to Maximise On Play
これに加えて Maximize on Play では
the game view also has a Stats button
ゲームビューには統計（Stats）ボタンがあり
to allow you to see performance statistics
自身のゲームに関する
based on your game
様々なパフォーマンス統計を見ることができて
and also the ability to show Gizmos in the same
さらに Gizmo を
way that the Scene view shows them already.
シーンビューで表示される場合と同様に使用されます。
As you can adjust things whilst in play mode
再生モードで調整することが出来るために
you should also be aware
覚えておくべきこととして
that any changes that you make will be undone
プロジェクトに戻ると、行った変更は
when returning to your project.
全て元に戻ります。
This is specific to changes that are
これはシーンにおけるゲームオブジェクトに対する変更
based on game objects in your scene
が対象であり、
and not game objects that refgerence assets in the project.
プロジェクトで参照されるゲームオブジェクトに関する変更では異なります。
For example if I was to change something relating to a material
例えば、マテリアルに関連して何かを変更したとき、
that change is made to the original asset.
その変更はもとのアセットに対して反映されます。
Whereas if I was to change something on a specific component
これに対して、特定のコンポーネントに関連して何かを変更するとき、
that change will be undone when play is pressed again.
Play ボタンを再び押した後、その変更は失われます。
It's also worth being aware
注意すべき点として
that when you press play, your game is running
Play ボタンを押下するとゲームは実行されていて
and you can hint this by going to
これを分かりやすく色表示するには
Unity - Preferences on Mac
Mac 上では Unity - Preferences を選択するか
or Edit - Preferences on PC.
PC 上では Edit - Preferences を選択します。
You can choose under Colours
Colors メニューの下で
a play mode tint,
再生モードの色を網掛けすることが出来ます。
I've chosen a shade of blue,
今回は青色の網掛けにしてみました。
but I can make this any colour that I need to.
この色は好みに応じて任意の色に変更できます。
That way, when you press play
これによって、Play ボタンを押下すると
the rest of the interface will change to this colour.
インタフェースの残りの部分はこの色に変更されます。
This is to remind you that you are in
これは Play モードに入っていることを示すものであり
play mode and will lose changes
その状態で行っている変更作業は後で失われることを
if you continue to work in that mode.
教えてくれます。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)